(Sheldon:)Look at Dr. Saul Perlmutter up there
clutching that Nobel Prize.
(Sheldon:)What's the matter, Saul?
Afraid someone's gonna steal it?
(Sheldon:)Like you stole Einstein's
cosmological constant?
(Leonard:)You know what?
I am tired of living in fear of this guy.
(Leonard:)I'm gonna go see him...
...and say the things
I should have said in high school.
"Pick on someone your own size."
"No, you did not have sex
with my mother."
And, "Yes, I do know
why I'm hitting myseIf."
Oh. Now Perlmutter shaking
the king's hand.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. Check for your watch,
Gustaf, he might've lifted it.
(Bernadette:)I love this dress.
(Bernadette:)- How come I never see you wear it?
- Because when I wear it, it's a shirt.
(Penny:)So, what's Howard doing tonight?
(Bernadette:)Oh, they all went with Leonard
to confront his childhood bully.
Oh. Terrific. High-school quarterback
against four mathletes.
(Amy:)When Leonard gets back,
I'd love to check serotonin levels.